dedicatednow.com 2010-12-29

# DedicatedNOW: Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices adopted by the DedicatedNOW, Inc. site.

DedicatedNOW takes your privacy very seriously and is committed to safeguard your private information. The Privacy Policy governs the approach of the DedicatedNOW website to gather, use, and preserve the information of its users. DedicatedNOW reserves the right to amend its policy at any time. Therefore, we advise our visitors to periodically check the website for updates.

### Information gathered by DedicatedNOW

At the time of availing web hosting services from us, it is mandatory for you to endow us with some personal information.

The type of information collected on DedicatedNOW is:

> Name  
>  Company  
>  Address  
>  Email address  
>  Phone number  
>  Fax number  
>  Credit/Debit Card Information  
>  Domain name 

Once you sign up for our service, you may need to communicate with us regarding any matter associated with our services. We may maintain the information related to the communication with our customers for future use. Whenever we transmit or receive sensitive information, we readdress the visitors to a secure server and notify them via security icon, which appears on the visitor's browser.

### How We Use this Information?

DedicatedNOW may use your personally identifiable information, which is accumulated, to contact the customers regarding the services and products offered by DedicatedNOW. The information is used to an extent agreed upon by the user. We may use this information for research purposes, which is shared with the advertisers and helps in better design and effective use of our website. For example: The research statistics help us to tell the advertisers the number of the individuals who visited a certain area of our site or the number of women and men, registered on our site, but at no cost shall we disclose any information that would identify an individual.

### Review, Correction of Information and Deactivation of Membership

Registered customers can access, review, and edit their personal information stored in the DedicatedNOW's database at any time. Follow the instructions provided in your account to review the information.

You can rectify the factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request mentioning the error. We also provide you the facility to promptly update the information on your own. We take appropriate steps to check your authenticity before permitting you to make changes.

A customer may choose to cancel his/her services with DedicatedNOW. Upon cancellation, your personal information is removed from DedicatedNOW's database. Remember that because of records of deletion and backups, it may be impracticable to delete all information related to an individual.

### Log Files/Cookies

DedicatedNOW's website uses Log Files. The information stored in the log files includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), browser type, platform type, referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to administer the site, track user's movement and collect information for aggregate use. Our log file does not contain personally identifiable information.

DedicatedNOW, Inc. also uses cookies, which make the site secure and run smoothly. Cookies limit the appearance of popup windows and ensure proper tracking of the website by users. DedicatedNOW supports persistent cookies to remember user's information like password, every time he/she visits the DedicatedNOW site.

### Your Responsibility

It is your sole responsibility to secure your Customer ID and Password. Therefore, it is advisable not to share them with others. To deny others from accessing your private information always keep in mind to log out, once your session expires. This not only applies when you are using a public computer, but even when using your personal computer at home.

### Children policy

You should be at least 13 years of age to have our permission to use our site. Our website is structured not to attract anyone below 13 years of age and as per our policy, we do not gather information knowingly from anybody who is under 13 years of age.

### Security

DedicatedNOW makes the best possible efforts to protect the user's sensitive information both online and offline. Access to all the information pertaining to the users is restricted in our office. Permission to access the personally identifiable information of the users is only granted to the employees such as the customer service representatives or the billing clerks, who need it to perform a certain job. Our employees are advised to use password protected screen savers whenever they leave their computers. Our servers that store the personally identifiable information are housed in a secured environment behind locked cage.

### Privacy Policy Changes

DedicatedNOW policies are subject to change anytime without prior notification. Any changes made to DedicatedNOW's policies are posted on our site. If you do not agree to our privacy policy, then please do not use our site. Continued use of DedicatedNOW's website by the customers, after the changes have been posted on the website will indicate their acceptance for the change. If you have any question regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
